关于基因改良过的星际战士
What's the best first-person shooter
最棒的第一人称射击游戏是什么
about genetically modified space marines?
侬好呀[光晕游戏]
Halo!
亲爱的
Honey,
你是不是玩了你新买的游戏一整天了
have you been playing your new little video game all day?
你用这种语气说出来 表明卢克和我
When you say it in that tone, it implies that Luke and I
没有好好共度父子亲密时光
haven't been spending quality time together.
-其实是有的 -我能跟他说话吗
- Which we have. - Can I talk to him?
当然了 卢克
Sure thing. Luke!
我觉得他好像不在
I don't think he's here.
我是说 我知道他不在
I mean, I-I know he's not here.
他去哪儿了
Where is he?
我相信他一定和他的小伙伴一起出去了
I am certain he is probably out with his usual crew of cut-ups.
你没有洗衣服吧
You're not doing laundry, are you?
没 但你叮嘱过的话 我马上就去洗
God, no. But I'm about to if I'm supposed to.
不 不 不要洗
No, no. Don't. Don't.
但你能在我回家前
But can you vacuum out
把通风管道清理干净吗
the dryer vent before I get home?
我一定会清理的
I will absolutely do that.
谢了
Thanks.
我联系不上海莉了
I can't get in touch with Haley.
自从我们吵架后 我就没跟她说上话
I haven't talked to her since we got in that fight.
她在吗
She around?
我觉得她好像去朋友家过夜了
I think she slept at a friend's house.
什么朋友
What friend?
不是个常见的名字
Not a normal name,
是元音开头的 很可能是个外国人
starts with a vowel, possibly foreign.
或许艾丽克斯知道 她在家吗
Oh, maybe Alex knows. Is she home?
不在 我已经好几个小时没见到她了
Nope. I have not seen her for hours.
海莉认识个叫阿杰巴的人吗
Does Haley know an Arjibarge?
-嗨 妈 -嗨 宝贝 你在哪儿呢
- Hi, mom. - Hi, honey. Where are you?
我在厨房啊
I'm in the kitchen.
艾丽克斯 你什么时候回家的啊
Alex? When'd you get home?
我一整天都在家里啊
I've been here all day.
你该多出去 呼吸下新鲜空气什么的
You should get outside, get some fresh air.
现在是美好的清晨时光
It's a beautiful morning.
都已经中午了 而且外面冷死了
It's noon, and it's freezing out.
菲尔 亲爱的 我不在家时
Phil, honey, when I'm not home,
我需要你站好岗 看好每一个孩子
I need you to be present and keep track of everyone.
听上去很棒 我也爱你
Sounds good. Love you, too.
艾丽克斯 你知道海莉去哪儿了吗
Alex, do you know where Haley is?
我知道她昨晚去给莉莉当保姆了
I mean, I know she was babysitting Lily last night,
但从那之后我就没见过她了
but I haven't seen her since.
顺便说下
By the way,
别看我昨晚发你的我大学申请论文的草稿
don't read the draft I sent you last night of my college essay.
我刚刚又重新发给你了一份
I just sent you a new version.
好的 我这就去看
Uh, okay. I will go read that one right now.
天啊 你在干什么 你在拍我吗
Oh, my god. What are you doing? Are you filming me?
是的 我想让你看看你的表现有多疯狂
Yes! I want you to see how crazy you are acting.
我? 我去找你说一件很重要的事
Me?! I come to talk to you about something important,
然后你就拿着摄像机跟着我狂拍
and then you start chasing me aound with the camera.
我9小时前就吩咐过你打扫厨房了
I asked you to clean up the kitchen nine hours ago
当时是我离家去上班时
when I left for work.
等我下班回到家 发现还是脏乱的一片
I come back, and it's the exact same mess,
还多了腌黄瓜和花生酱
plus pickles and peanut butter!
我整天都得为我那个疯狂的老板做各种事
I was running around doing stuff for my crazy boss all day,
然后我饿了
and then I got hungry,
但垃圾桶里的臭味差点让我吐出来
and then the smell from the garbage almost made me throw up!
我也是这种感觉
That's exactly how I feel!
别烦我了
Leave me alone!
我的烦心事已经够多的了[盘子上很多脏东西]
I have a lot on my plate!
是的 是的 我看到了 亲爱的
Yes. Yes, I can see that, honey.
你把脏盘子都堆在洗碗池里了
You left it in the sink!
天啊
Oh, my god!
我排了两小时的队 但总算买到了
I waited in line for two hours, but I got it.
哎呀 我们在拍家庭录像吗
Ooh, we making a home movie?
喂
Hello?
你好 老爸
Hey, dad.
爸 把手机从耳朵旁边拿下来
Dad, take the phone away from your ear.
为什么要拿下来
Why would I do this?
现在我听不到你说话了
Now I can't hear you.
放在你面前
Put it in front of your face.
你怎么跑到我手机里的
How'd you get in my phone?
这是不是意味着那天我们通话时
Does this mean when we talked the other day
你知道我是在厕所里
that you knew I was in the can?
我这下知道了
I do now.
会议展示做得怎么样
How was the presentation?
非常顺利
Actually went really well.
客户喜欢我们的新设计
The client loves the whole re-design.
但希望我们换掉长方形把手
They just want us to swap out the handles --
-该死的 -我懂的
- Damn it! - I know.
只有蠢货才会想要旋钮
Only knobs want knobs.
不是 是乔咬了我 他在出牙
No, Joe bit me. He's teething.
我觉得安迪这周末请假
I don't think it's a coincidence
不是巧合
that Andy took the weekend off.
这孩子跟海狸似的
Kid's like a beaver.
我都不敢穿短裤了
I'm afraid to wear short pants.
好啊 克莱尔
Hola, Claire.
好啊 歌洛莉亚
Hey, Gloria.
出差怎么样 玩得开心吗
How's your trip? Are you having any fun?
是啊 风有点大 但是
Uh...yeah. You know, it's a little windy, but, eh.
你同意我帮卢克剪头发吧
So, you're okay with me cutting Luke's hair, right?
-妈妈 -好啊
- Hey, mom. - Well, hello.
知道你没死在某个小巷里真是太好了
It's nice to know you're not dead in an alley somewhere.
你也是
Right back at you.
我同意你剪他的头发
Yes, I am fine with you cutting his hair.
两边别留太长就行
Just don't leave it too long on the sides.
我很擅长剪男孩的头发
I am very good cutting boys' hair.
你以后该让我剪你的
You should let me cut yours someday.
好吧 再见 歌洛莉亚
Okay, bye-bye, Gloria.
你还在吗
You still there?
该死 爸 你知道今天是
Crap. Dad, did you know
米奇尔的生日吗
it was Mitchell's birthday today?
当然啦 我已经给他打了电话
Of course. I already called him
因为我是个体贴周到的人
because I'm a considerate person
对家人由衷地关心
who really cares about his family.
是我提醒的他 我拨的电话
I reminded him and dialed the phone.
旅途顺利
Fly safe.
记住你可以向后靠[倒退]
And remember you can recline.
到了天上也还是美国
It's still America up there.
谢了 老爸
Thanks, dad.
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
好啊 还是我的生日吗
Oh, hey. Is it still my birthday?
小心点 不然我要唱歌了
Watch it, or I'll sing to you.
-生... -好吧 我认输
-Ha-- - Okay, okay, I give.
好吧 你今天过得好吗
Okay. So, have you had a good day?
不错 谢谢
Yes, thank you.
莉莉
Uh, Lily,
她给我做了她拿手的巧克力豆炒蛋
she made me her famous chocolate-chip scrambled eggs...
她还看着我吃了下去
...which she then watched me eat.
是的
Yeah.
你收到我的礼物了吧
You got my present, didn't you?
没有
No.
该死 他们跟我保证会按时送到
Darn it. They promised it would be there on time.
我等不及拆开礼物
Oh, well, I can't wait to open it
看看发票上的日期了
and check the date on the invoice.
-那是克莱尔吗 -是
- Hey, is that Claire? - Yeah.
-好啊 克莱尔 -好啊
- Hi, Claire! - Hi.
你给她看了我的礼物吗
Hi. Hey, uh, did you, uh, show her my gift yet?
没有
No.
-快给她看啊 -好的 好
- Come on, show her, show her. - Okay. Yeah.
超棒
It's good.
您好 生日快乐[模仿犹太人]
Wow, shalom and chh-appy birthday.
就是啊
I know, right?
很棒吧
Isn't it fantastic?
克莱尔 你给我买加勒特奶酪
Hey, Claire, did you get me some Garrett's cheese
和焦糖味爆米花了吗
and caramel corn yet?
糟糕 我忘了
Oh, shoot, I forgot.
你在芝加哥就只用做这件事啊
It's the one thing you had to do in Chicago!
你太对了
You are so right.
很抱歉 我因为工作分心了
I'm sorry that I let myself get distracted by my job.
我要的是甜中带咸 克莱尔
Okay, I'm looking for sweet and salty, Claire,
不是苦的[尖酸]
not bitter.
别激动 小卡
Relax, Cam.
这里肯定有小卖部卖那个
I'm sure there's a kiosk around here that sells it.
那就好
Good.
听着 昨天海莉有没有提起过
Guys, listen, yesterday, did Haley mention
她照看莉莉之后要去哪里
where she was gonna go after she babysat for Lily?
没有 但你找到她时
No, but when you do talk to her,
能不能告诉她
can you tell her
让她小心对待我的粉蓝色西装
to please be careful with my powder-blue suit
那是小卡未经我同意借给她的
that Cam let her borrow without asking me?
她为什么需要西装
Why did she want a suit?
她的一个朋友参加婚礼用的
A friend of hers needs it for a wedding,
米奇尔得摆脱
and Mitchell needs to stop
"理发店四重唱"的造型
dressing like he's in a barbershop quartet.
莉莉 亲爱的
Lily, honey,
海莉离开时有没有说她要去哪里
did Haley say where she was going when she left here?
-谁想知道 -克莱尔姑妈
- Who wants to know? - Aunt Claire.
克莱尔姑妈 听说你对海莉很刻薄
Hey, Aunt Claire. I heard you were being mean to Haley.
我没对海莉很刻薄
I was not mean to Haley.
行了 你在嚷嚷
Okay, you're screaming.
我不知道她去了哪里 也许迪兰知道
I don't know where she went. Maybe Dylan knows.
迪兰 他怎么会知道
Dylan? Why would Dylan know?
他来过 他们在沙发上说话
He came over, and they were talking on the couch
我那时候在另一间房里
while I was in the other room...
很乖的
behaving.
她还在跟迪兰说话吗 真的吗
She's still talking to Dylan? Really?
等等 我得挂了
Oh, wait, guys, I got to go.
生日快乐 芭芭拉[《燕特尔》主演]
Uh, happy birthday, Babs.
那是什么意思
What does she mean by that?
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
别读上一封草稿
Oh, don't read that last draft.
我刚改了第三段
I just changed something in paragraph three.
真糟糕
Oh, oh, that's too bad.
第三段有我最喜欢的...
Paragraph three had some of my favorite --
拜托 我能看见你的眼睛
Oh, please, I can see your eyes
在飞快浏览屏幕
darting around the screen.
读新的那篇就好
Just read the new one.
你能不能帮我个忙 给你姐姐打电话
Can you just do me a favor and call your sister?
如果她在屏蔽来电 我肯定打不进去
If she's screening, I'm not making the cut.
你何不偷窥她的Facebook页面
Why don't you just snoop on her facebook page
用你的假个人主页
with your fake profile?
我没有假的个人主页
I don't have a fake profile.
妈你算了吧 布罗迪·肯德尔刚上线了
Mom, save it. Brody Kendall just logged in.
这种把戏也许能骗骗海莉
That trick might've worked on Haley,
但我知道照片是察琪的
but I know that's a picture of Chachi.
天呐 不是吧
Oh, my God. What?
告诉我这不过是个错误
Please tell me that's some kind of mistake!
哪里 哪一段
Where? Which paragraph?
去叫你爸来 马上
Get your father -- now!
爸 老妈找你
Dad, mom needs you!
告诉她我在洗澡
Tell her I'm in the shower!
亲爱的 我们该打给谁 该怎么办
Honey, who do we call? What do we do?
海莉怎么可能结婚了
There's no way Haley's married.
那她为什么换了Facebook的状态
Then why did she change her Facebook status?
她应该没有吧
She probably didn't.
可能是电脑的问题 有人黑了她的账号
It could be a computer glitch, someone hacked her account.
我觉得在知道真相前我们都该冷静点
I just think we should stay calm until we know the story.
亲爱的 失去联系又不清楚情况
Honey, I cannot get on a plane for four hours
你叫我怎么在飞机上待四个小时
and be out of touch and not know what happened!
不只是Facebook
It's not just the Facebook thing.
她从米奇尔那里借了一件婚礼用的蓝西装
She borrowed a blue suit from Mitchell for a wedding.
借来的 蓝色的[婚礼习俗]
Something borrowed, something blue?
你意识到了吗
Do you get it?
她要嫁给谁呢
Who would she even marry?
我不知道 但她昨天跟迪兰在一起
I don't know, but she was with Dylan yesterday,
如果她要跟他结婚
and if she was gonna marry him,
她肯定不会告诉我们
she would definitely hide that from us.
可是说不通啊 他为什么不打给我
But that makes no sense. Why wouldn't he call me?
-你好 邓太太 -你好 迪兰
- Oh, hey, Mrs. "D". - Hey, Dylan!
你好 邓先生
Oh, hi, Mr. "D"!
-你跟海莉在一起吗 -以什么方式
- Are you with Haley? - In what way?
现实中 浪漫里 婚姻性质地
Physically, romantically, maritally?
不 我在工作呢 我有事业了
No. I'm at work. I have a career now.
你能帮我拿一下电话吗
Hey, uh, can you hold this phone for a second?
所以你不知道海莉现在在哪里
So, you have no idea where Haley is right now?
你是说精神上 还是地理上
You mean spiritually, geographically?
你能别转那个广告牌了吗
Can you please stop spinning that sign?
不行 我老板说我要是停了
No. My boss says if I do,
他就找个那种人来取代我
he'll replace me with one of those guys!
回你来的地方去
Go back to where you came from!
迪兰 看着我
Dylan, focus!
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is,
不过我能感觉到她没事
but I can sense that she's okay.
就像我们共用一个大脑一样
It's like we share the same brain.
现在脑子在谁那
Who has it now?
好了 昨晚你跟她在一起时
Okay, so, last night when you were with her,
她完全没说要结婚的事吗
she didn't say anything about getting married?
海莉结婚了吗 太让人伤心了
Haley got married?! That's so upsetting!
好了
Done.
-妈 -你有海莉的iCloud密码吗
- Hi, mom. - Do you have Haley's iCloud Password?
是的 她放在一个小信封里
Yeah, she gave it to me in a little envelope
跟她的日记本钥匙
with her diary key
以及最怕的事物清单一起交给了我
and a list of things she's most afraid of.
也许我们能猜出来
Maybe we could guess it.
克莱尔 你不小心把电话挂了
Claire, you accidentally hung up on me.
对 亲爱的 你知道我不太会用电脑
Oh, yeah, well, honey, you know me and computers.
妈妈在猜海莉的iCloud密码
Mom's trying to guess Haley's iCloud password.
个人觉得这侵犯了她的隐私
Which, personally, I think is an invasion of her privacy.
试试看"密码"行不行
Ooh, try "Password."
还好不是这个
I'm kind of glad that didn't work.
等等 我记得我告诉过她
Wait, I think I remember telling her to use something
要用别人不知道的东西做密码
that people wouldn't know about her,
比如她最喜欢的文学形象
like her favorite literary character.
进去了
I'm in!
不是吧 是什么
What? What was it?
史努比[爱窥探的]
Snoopy.
可以当你的新外号了
And that could be your new nickname.
好吧 寻找我的iPhone
Okay. Find my iPhone.
不是吧 她在拉斯维加斯
Oh, no! She's in Vegas.
你没开玩笑吧
Are you serious?
等等 我在放大 等等 等等
Oh, hang on. I'm zooming in. Hold on, hold on.
我来看看...
Let me see what I can, uh...
快点
Come on.
天呐
And -- oh, God!
亲爱的 她在一间婚礼教堂里
Honey, she's at a wedding chapel!
好吧 是有点麻烦 但是你想想
Okay, that's troubling, but think about it.
如果她没跟迪兰在一起 她能跟谁结婚
If she's not with Dylan, who would she be marrying?
我不知道
I don't know!
艾丽克斯 她一定跟你说过什么
Alex, she had to have told you something!
好吧 我们确实不亲密
Okay, you are really rubbing in our lack of closeness.
她连用什么护发素都不会告诉我
She won't even tell me what conditioner she uses.
我只有12分钟了 赶紧想
I have 12 minutes! Think!
我不知道 去问米尔奇舅舅吧
I don't know. Ask uncle Mitchell.
她们总是聊男孩子的事
They're always giggling about boys.
好 我这就找他
Oh, good! Okay, yes, I'm gonna do that.
我打给他
I'm calling him.
要是有用
If it helps,
我可以找我在赌城的魔术师朋友
I can alert my magician contacts in Vegas.
尽管他们更擅长让女孩消失
Although, they are better at making girls disappear
而不是把她们找出来
than they are finding them.
什么事
What?
莉莉 亲爱的 去帮我叫米奇尔
Lily, honey, I need you get Mitchell.
他们说我能玩20分钟iPad
But they said I could have 20 minute of iPad time.
米奇尔 米奇尔
Mitchell? Mitchell?!
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
我得跟米奇尔谈谈
I-I really need to talk to Mitchell.
现在是我的iPad时间
It's my iPad time!
宝贝 关于自私这事我怎么跟你说的
Honey, what did I tell you about being selfish?
只要克莱尔姨妈买到我要的爆米花
Aunt Claire needs to speak to other daddy
她就能跟二爸说话啦
just as soon as she gets me my popcorn.
什么 小卡 我说过了
What? You, Cam, I promise you,
我会给你买到爆米花的
I will get you your popcorn,
但现在我得跟米奇尔谈谈
but right now, I need to talk to Mitchell!
-奶酪和焦糖味的 -知道了
- Okay, cheese and caramel. - Fine.
-还有焦糖味的 -记住了
- And caramel. - Fine.
怎么了
Hey, what's up?
我很确定海莉在赌城结婚了
So, I'm pretty sure that Haley is getting married in Vegas.
-你说什么 -什么
- What?! - What?!
我要知道她在和谁约会
Yeah, I need to know who she's been dating.
她说过自己可能喜欢上了
T-there was this one guy who she thought
这么一个人 但我也不清楚
that she might like, but, I don't know.
她对于他一直藏着掖着
She was weirdly secretive about him,
我觉得那个人算一个约会对象吧
but I-I guess that could still be thing.
等等 老爸打电话来了
Oh, hang on, hang on, getting a call from dad.
快做
Do the thing.
做那个可爱的动作
Do the cute thing.
-爸 -克莱尔
- Dad? - Claire?
-爸 -米奇尔
- Dad? - Mitchell?
你们在我手机里做什么
What are you doing in my phone?
你打给我的 老爸
You called me, dad.
我没有 我在跟乔拍视频
No, I didn't. I'm shooting a video with Joe.
我现在在你的厨房里吗
Am I in your kitchen with you?
不在
No.
所以你没在跟乔拍视频
Then you're not shooting a video with Joe.
杰 你好 克莱尔要去办点事
Hi, Jay! Claire was just about to go run an errand!
没搞错吧
Are you kidding me?!
天呐 等着
Okay, for God sakes. Hold--
能麻烦您帮我看一下电脑吗
would you mind watching my computer for me for a minute?
-非常感谢 -不客气
- Thank you so much. - Of course, dear.
米奇尔 我喜欢这顶新帽子
Hey, Mitch, I'm liking the new hat.
-让你看起来不一样了 -你想说什么
- It gives you some presence. - What you getting at, dad?
没想说什么啊 就是很硬汉
Nothing. It's a strong look.
你看起来像以前西部片里的型男
Y-you like one of those tough guys in an old western movie.
-真的吗 -真的
- Really? - Yeah.
这个帽子有点反派气息
Oh, I guess it is kind of badass.
如果我把它往后折一点呢
What if I tilt it a little bit?
那就毁了
You ruined it.
我喜欢你的帽子 很配
I like your hat. It suits you.
谢谢你 女士
Oh, thank you, ma'am.
不客气
Well, you're welcome.
谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
把你改变人生的爆米花买回来了
All right, got your life-changing popcorn.
真棒
Yes!
能说回海莉结婚这件事了吗
Now, can we get back to figuring out who Haley married?
海莉结婚了
Haley got married?!
千万别是跟杰克逊
Oh my gosh, I hope it was no to Jackson.
杰克逊
Jackson!
他喜欢很奇怪的...食物
He was into some weird food.
完蛋了
Oh, God!
海莉结婚了 她麻烦大了
Whoa, Haley got married?! She is in so much trouble!
卢克 你的头发怎么了
Luke, what have you done to your hair?!
克莱尔 你这种反应
Claire, when you react like this,
正是他想看到的
you're just giving him what he wants.
卢克说你知道的
Luke said that you knew about it!
我不知道
I didn't know about it!
我说有家长知道
I said a parent knew about it.
菲尔
Phil!
我知道还没到这步
I know we're not there yet,
但我在网上搜了婚姻无效条约
but I've been researching annulments.
就要到这步了
Oh, we are there
因为你同意他剪莫霍克发型
because you let our child get a Mohawk!
真棒
Sweet!
我们打了个赌
We...had a bet.
他赢了你就让他留这头型吗
You let him get a Mohawk because he won a bet?!
-他输了 -什么 菲尔
- No, he lost the bet. - What?! Phil!
难道你想让我留莫霍克发型吗
Well, I-I, would you rather I had a Mohawk?
-我可是要上班的 -我没时间争论
- I have a career. - I-I don't have time for this.
我们得搞清楚
We've got to get back to figuring out
海莉在赌城和谁结的婚
who Haley has married in Vegas.
-有人敲门 -好吧
- Hold on. Someone's at the door.- Okay.
海莉在赌城吗
So, Haley's in Vegas?
-对 -你想的话 我可以打给安迪
- Yes. - If you want, I can call Andy.
他也在 也许他能找到她
He's there, too. Maybe he can find her.
安迪在赌城
Andy's in Vegas?
是啊 他问我借了袖扣
Yeah, he borrowed some cuff links
说是婚礼要用
from me for some wedding.
天呐
Oh, my God,
海莉不会嫁给安迪了吧
you guys don't think that Haley married Andy, do you?
-海莉嫁给了安迪 -什么
- Haley married Andy! - What?!
-他又赌输了什么 -不 不
- What bet did he lose? - No, no, no, no, no, no.
安迪在和犹他州那女孩约会
Andy is dating some girl in Utah,
海莉知道的
and Haley knows that.
就算海莉喜欢他
Even if Haley was attracted to him,
我也希望她有点自尊心
I would hope she would have the decency
和自控能力
and the self-control--
天呐 她嫁给了安迪
Oh, my God! Oh, my god, she married Andy!
我就知道她还喜欢他
I knew she was still into him.
她说他俩不合适 但我就说
She said he wasn't her type, but I'm like,
"他是个男的 有呼吸的男的"
"He's a man. He's breathing."
也许这就是她不和我聊天的原因
Maybe this is why she doesn't talk to me about things.
不可能是他 他是个好小伙
No, it can't be him. He's a very nice boy.
克莱尔 相信我
Claire, trust me,
安迪不会和海莉私奔的
Andy's not gonna run off and elope with Haley.
他是个正直的人
He's a stand-up guy.
-是寄给海莉的包裹 -打开
- It's a package for haley. - Open it.
这侵犯她隐...
Well, that seems like an invasion of her priv--
打开
Open it!
《孕期指南》
"What to expect when you're expecting."
老天啊
Oh, my god!
我就说他是个正"直"的男人
I told you he was a stand-up guy.
她不接电话 菲尔
She's not answering, phil.
你在给安迪打电话吗
Are you calling andy?
直接转到语音信箱了
It's going straight to voice mail.
我不敢相信她怀孕了
I can't believe she's pregnant.
别轻易下结论
Let's not jump to any conclusions.
轻易吗 来回顾一下
Jump? Let's review.
她情绪暴躁 吃奇怪的东西
She's been moody, eating weird food,
恶心反胃
getting nauseous.
她半夜离家
She left in the middle of the night
和秘密爱人跑去拉斯维加斯小教堂
for a wedding chapel in vegas with her secret love,
还有最可疑的是 她买了一本书
and most suspicious of all, she bought a book!
糟了 如果你是对的该怎么办
Oh, no. What if you're right?
-我们该怎么做 -我不知道
- What will we do? - I don't know.
我要灭了那个安迪
I'll kill that Andy.
他怎么能这么不负责任
How could he be so irresponsible?
他虽然是个好人
I mean, he's a good kid.
他怎么能就这么拐走我的女儿
But to run off with my baby girl
之前还让我迷上他的"道歉"表演
after I fell for his "Aw, shucks" act!
也可能不是表演 因为他人很好
Which is probably not an act because he's genuinely nice
还有他觉得那是脏话
and he thinks "Shucks" is the "S" word.
我还是想灭了他
Still, I want to kill him!
但我的外孙可能就
But that would be robbing my grandchild
没了一个超棒的爸爸
of probably a really great father.
去你的 安迪·贝利
Damn you, Andy Bailey!
他姓贝利吗
His last name is Bailey?
老天啊 她以后要叫海莉·贝利了
Oh, my god, she's gonna be Haley Bailey.
-等等 我想到一件事 -什么事
- Wait. I just thought of something. - What?
我成了家里第一个
I'm going to be the first woman in my family
没因为怀孕从大学退学的女人
not to get pregnant and drop out of college.
也许我论文该写这个
Ooh, maybe that should be my essay.
老娘大学毕业了啊
I graduated from college.
没错 而且海莉退学时
Yeah, and haley got kicked out of college
还没怀孕呢
before she got pregnant.
等一下 亲爱的 我给你发张图片
Okay, hang on, honey. I am sending you a picture.
你觉得这个纵火犯像留胡子的安迪吗
Do you think that this arsonist looks like Andy with a beard?
不 他不是纵火犯
No. He's not an arsonist.
歌洛莉亚请他照顾孩子呢
Gloria hired him to take care of her baby.
对了 问问歌洛莉亚
Gloria. Right, of course.
你知道她保护欲有多强
You know how protective she is.
她肯定仔细查过他的底细
I'm sure she had him thoroughly vetted.
你好
Hola!
歌洛莉亚 你在哪找到的安迪
Gloria, where did you find Andy?
公园里 当时他在追小孩
At the park, chasing some children.
-天呐 -我再给他打电话
- Oh, my god. - I'm gonna call him again.
老妈快看
Hey, mom, check it out.
天呐 卢克你做了什么
God, Luke, what have you done?!
就是 他有什么必要叛逆
I know. What does he have to rebel against?
海莉怀孕 我留着莫霍克发型
Haley pregnant and me in a Mohawk --
今年圣诞节贺卡的全家福我们无敌啦
This year's christmas card is gonna rule.
进展如何 你找到她了吗
What's going on? Did you find her?
没 爸 我没找到她 你知道吗
No, dad, no, I haven't found her. And you know what?
这都是你的错
This is all your fault
因为你们俩把
because you two introduced
这个饥渴的陌生人带进了我们的生活
this horny stranger into our lives.
让我搞搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
你生气是因为你女儿怀孕
You're mad because your daughter got knocked up
和一个猥琐男私奔
and ran off with some goofy guy
然后背着你结婚
to get married behind your back.
我都想象不到那是种什么感觉
I can't even imagine what that must feel like.
真的 你现在要演这出
Really? Now?
没有比现在更好的时机了
I can't think of a better time.
杰 不要落进下石了
Jay, stop kicking her while she's down,
也不要点破
pointing out her mistakes at the same time
她众人皆知的错误
the whole universe is telling her
她不就是个糟糕的母亲嘛
that she's a terrible mother!
天呐 听不下去了 我挂了 拜拜
Oh, my god, okay, can't do this. Got to go. Bye.
我想我的闺女
I miss my little girl!
克莱尔 别那么做
Claire, don't do that.
对 克莱尔 别那么做
Yes, Claire, don't do that!
听着
Look...
你闺女不在罐子底
You're not gonna find her at the bottom of that tin.
你还没吃到罐子底 对吧
You're not near the bottom of that tin, are you?
我要当外婆了
I'm gonna be a grandmother!
没事的 宝贝
Aww, there, there, dear.
好了 克莱尔
Okay, Claire...
现在什么都还不确定
We don't know anything for sure yet.
深呼吸
So take a deep breath...
放下爆米花
...put the popcorn down...
然后振...
And just get your...
太不地道了 外婆
Not cool, grandma!
好了 克莱尔 听我说
Okay, Claire, listen, listen.
有时候生活给你你不想要的东西
Sometimes life hands you things that you don't want
但最后你却发现那正是你需要的
and -- and they turn out to be exactly what you need.
天呐
And, oh, my god,
我刚刚说服自己喜欢上这顶帽子了
I think I just talked myself into liking this hat
因为在屏幕上看到自己
because I keep seeing myself in it,
我心里的潜台词是"这帅小伙是谁啊"
and I'm like, "Who is that handsome Yentl man?
你没开玩笑吧
Are you serious right now?
天呐 我得挂了
Oh, god, I got to go.
对不起 我没帮上忙 你还好吗
I'm sorry. I wasn't that helpful. Are you okay?
我们的女儿居然背着我们结婚了
Our little baby got married without us.
我本应该送她出嫁的
I was supposed to give her away.
我本应该牵着她的手走过红毯
I was supposed to walk her down the aisle
然后对她的未来丈夫这样说
and give her husband-to-be one of these.
她是我的宝贝女儿
"That's my baby girl.
你一定要照顾好她
You take care of her."
-没错 -那就是老爸该做的事
- Yeah. - 'Cause that's what dads do.
我要给我爸打电话
I got to call my dad.
拜托别告诉他
Please don't tell him
她是在我的看管下离开的
I was in charge when she left.
喂 看得到我吗
Hello. Can you see me?
手指头 爸
Thumb, dad.
他们淘汰老式旋转电话的那一刻
The minute they got rid of rotary phones,
一切都完蛋了
everything went to hell.
爸 真抱歉我以前私奔了
Dad, I'm really sorry that I eloped.
你是个非常优秀的老爸
You were a great dad,
你本该牵着我的手走过红毯
and you should've been there to walk me down the aisle,
然后
and --
我剥夺了你的这项权利 却从未道歉
and I've never apologized for taking that away from you.
我们后来在夏威夷做过了 那也很好啊
Well, we got to do that thing in Hawaii, and that was nice.
是 真是一报还一报啊
Yeah. Guess what goes around comes around, huh?
你现在正处在龙卷风的中心
Look...you're in the eye of the tornado right now,
除了看到你的生活席卷而来
and you can't see anything but
其它都看不到
your life swirling around you.
不过安迪是个好孩子 跟菲尔一样
But Andy's a good guy, just like Phil,
多年以后 你可能会回首往事
and years from now, you might look back on this
你会想 "最好的事情莫过于
and think, "The best thing that could've happened...
那个傻瓜把我女儿的肚子搞大了"
was that dipstick knocking up my daughter."
太感人了
That's so sweet.
-他一直在听吗 -是的
- Was he listening?! - Yeah.
这个傻瓜也爱你 杰
This dipstick loves you, too, Jay!
我把刚才的话收回
I take it all back!
-杰 -等一下 等一下
- Jay! - Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
我试着搞定它
I am trying to fix it!
歌洛莉亚在跟我说话 有些是英语
Gloria's talking to me. Some of it's in English.
克莱尔你看 我把卢克的发型整好了
Claire, Claire! Look, look, I fix Luke's hair!
老天呐 他看起来像善璞
Oh, my god, he looks like Shemp!
好吧 是很像 不过
Okay, yes, it's true, but --
也许如果我把这面再剪短一点...
but maybe if I cut a little bit more on the sides or in --
不 不要 别再剪了
Oh, no, no, no. No more cutting.
给我个机会习惯下就好了
Just give me a chance to get used to it.
-是海莉 海莉打来了 -什么
- Oh, it's Haley! Haley's calling! - What?!
妈妈
Hi, mom.
就跟我说这个吗
"Hi, mom"?!
我们一整天都试图联系你
We have been trying to get in touch with you all day!
-我一直在床上 -天呐
- I've been in bed. - Oh, goodness.
我们不需要听细节
I don't think we need to hear the details.
海莉 我们都知道了
Haley... we know everything.
我明白你为什么对我们隐瞒此事
And I understand why you hid it from us,
尽管我们很不高兴 年轻的女士
and while we are not happy, young lady,
我们可以一起想办法
we're gonna work this out.
在我承认什么事之前
Uh, before I admit to anything,
你能不能说得具体一点
maybe you could be more specific?
海莉 你在家啊
Haley! You're home!
是啊 我一整天都在家 一直在睡觉
Yeah, I've been home all day. I've been sleeping.
这么说你没结婚
So, you didn't get married?!
结婚 我为什么要结婚
Married?! Why would I get married?!
因为你怀了安迪的孩子
Because you're pregnant with Andy's baby!
什么 你为什么会那样想
What?! Why would you think that?!
因为你的Facebook状态改成了已婚
Because you changed your Facebook status to "Married"
而我们追踪你的手机
and then we tracked your cellphone
到赌城的一间婚礼教堂
to a wedding chapel in Vegas.
而且你还买了这本书
And you ordered this book!
首先 这叫隐私
Wow, first of all, it's called privacy.
不信去查
Google it.
第二 我嫁给了一个甜甜圈
Second, I married a cronut.
什么
What?
昨晚 我的朋友安迪和我
Last night, my friend Andy and I,
一起去买甜甜圈
we went to go get cronuts,
我说那些甜甜圈太好吃了
and I said that they were so amazing,
我真想嫁给它
I wanted to marry one,
所以我当笑话发到Facebook上的
so I posted it on Facebook as a joke.
后来我把手机落在安迪的车上了
Then I accidentally left my phone in Andy's car,
他开车去赌城参加朋友的婚礼
which he drove to a friend's wedding in Vegas,
那本书是给我的疯老板买的
and that book is for my crazy boss
他在设计孕妇装
because he's designing maternity clothes
想知道准妈妈们在想什么
and he wants to get inside the mind of preggos!
谢天谢地
Thank god!
真是松了一口气
I'm so relieved!
等等
Wait a second.
你怎么能看到我的Facebook页面
How did you get onto my Facebook page?
我没加你好友
I unfriended you.
那个布罗迪·肯德尔是她
She's Brody Kendall.
天呐 真恶心
Oh, my god, gross!
我居然一直在跟我妈玩糖果粉粹机
I've been playing Candy Crush with my mother!
你是怎么追踪到我的手机的
How did you track my phone?
我觉得那并不怎么重要
Well, I don't think that really matters,
而且我有充分的理由...
and there's a perfectly reasona--
省省吧 我能看到你后面有人走过
Oh, cut it out. I can see people walking behind you.
好了 我挂了
Okay, got to go.